facty.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Facty Network

This Privacy Policy was last revised and shall become effective as of **May 25, 2018**.   By accessing the Site, you have read and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy in its entirety.

  * If you opt-in to our newsletter(s), we’ll send you emails and other stuff that may be of interest to you. You can unsubscribe from our marketing emails at any time.
  * We collect Personal Data, Site Data, and Anonymous Data (as defined below) to make our website(s) more useful to you.
  * If we do collect Personal Data (as defined below), we will only use this information for lawful purposes and will store and retain this information for as long as required by applicable law.
  * You can contact us any time to update or remove any Personal Data that we have collected and stored about you.

Thank you for visiting facty.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of Assembly Technologies Inc. and its affiliated companies (“Assembly”, “our”, “we” or “us”). Assembly is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to describe to you and to outline our practices and policies associated with any information (such as Site Data, Anonymous Data, and Personal Data, each as defined below) that we may collect from you, or that you may share with us when you access or use the Site or use any related products and/or services.

### Lawful Basis for Processing Data

In certain jurisdictions, the processing of your Personal Data (as defined below) is lawful only if it is permitted under data protection legislation. In this case, we have a lawful basis for each of our processing activities (unless an exemption applies) as outlined below:

  * Consent. By using the Site, or otherwise submitting your Personal Data to us, you consent to our collection, use and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
  * Legitimate Interest. We will process your Personal Data based on Legitimate Interest, and particularly where it is used for marketing and business purposes, and to contact you to start a conversation regarding your use of the Site or any Assembly newsletters that you wish to join.
  * Legal Obligation. We may also process your Personal Data based on other lawful basis such as where the processing is necessary to comply with applicable law.

### How We Collect and Use Personal and Anonymous Data

When you access the Site, register for any associated products and/or services, or opt-in to receive newsletters and other communications from us, we may collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data from you. We may also collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data when you send us information or communications. “Personal Data” means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example and without limitation, your name, phone number, physical address, Internet Protocol (IP) address, and email address when you access the Site or any associated products and/or services. “Anonymous Data” refers to data about you that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data. Anonymous Data does not permit the identification of individual persons.

To make the Site more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you such as browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name, Site usage and statistics, and/or a date/time stamp of your visit to the Site. We may also use cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) and referring URLs to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit. We may also use Personal Data and Anonymous Data for market research purposes and to improve our services and the Site. We may share Anonymous Data with selected third parties and business partners, however, we will not share any Anonymous Data if such information is, contains, or will be linked to your Personal Data, unless we have given you notice, as described in this Privacy Policy, and you have given us authorization to do so. Assembly will use Personal Data and IP addresses to identify users of the Site if and when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Site’s policies, or to protect our services, the Site, or other users of the Site and/or services.

We may use Personal Data collected from you for the following general purposes:

(1) to fulfill your requests to receive information from us;  
(2) to improve the Site and our services;  
(3) to contact you to resolve problems;  
(4) to communicate with you about products and services offered by us and our selected partners;  
(5) to engage with third party service providers so that you can access and use the Site; and  
(6) to periodically conduct market research regarding your use of the Site and our services.

If and when we use a third party technical support provider, or third party hosting provider, we ensure that the same privacy criteria, as defined herein, are in place with such third parties. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen.

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Data. We will periodically send you newsletters and emails that directly promote the use of the Site or other third party products and/or services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to “opt-out” by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email you receive, or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Should you decide to opt-out of receiving future mailings from us, you may continue to receive future mailings from third parties that you have requested to receive information from. If you do not wish to receive future communications from third party providers, you should notify them directly of your choice regarding their use of your Personal Data. To opt-out of having future third party marketing communications sent to you, you will be required to unsubscribe with the applicable third party providers. Despite your request to no longer receive future newsletters or promotional and marketing communications from us, we reserve the right to continue to send you notices of any updates to the Site, our Terms of Use, and our Privacy Policy.

To learn more about your rights with respect to digital advertising, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). If you are located within the European Union, please visit [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

### How We Collect and Use Site Data

“Site Data” refers to data about how you use the Site. We may collect certain information from you including, but not limited to: User IP addresses, OS version, OS localization, device type, etc. We obtain this information from third party traffic monitoring service providers. Other than User IP address, the Site does not, and will not, collect any other Personal Data from you without your prior approval. The Site Data we collect is primarily used to report Site usage and statistics, to improve the Site, and to track the performance of various marketing initiatives. Site Data may also be used by Assembly to answer questions that customers have about their use of the Site.

### Sharing of Personal Data

We will never sell, trade, or rent any Personal Data, Site Data, or any Anonymous Data that may contain Personal Data, to any third party.

In certain special cases, we may disclose Personal Data when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, or is otherwise injuring or interfering with our rights, property or operations, other users of the Site, or anyone who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose your Personal Data and any Site Data when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case or administrative investigation.

If we determine, in our sole discretion, that you have engaged in conduct that might be considered unlawful, fraudulent, or might harm or damage the reputation or standing of Assembly with either the general public or with a business partner or potential business partner of Assembly, we reserve the right to release your Personal Data to such persons or third parties, as we consider necessary, to prevent you from causing injury to, or otherwise injuring or interfering, now or in the future, with our rights, property or operations or otherwise the rights, property or operations of anyone which could be harmed by such conduct.

### Cookies and Similar Technologies

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to your web browser by the Site. The cookie helps the Site remember information about your visit, which makes your next visit to the Site easier and the Site more useful to you. We also use cookies for tracking and reporting purposes, to make the ads that you may see more relevant to you, and to count how many visitors we receive to a page on the Site. The information collected by cookies is used to enhance your experience with on the Site, for marketing analysis, for targeted and display advertising, and for quality improvement of the Site and our services. No personally identifiable information is collected or stored by Assembly during this process. We may use your IP address to identify your general location for traffic monitoring purposes. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You are not required to accept cookies, however, if your browser rejects our cookies you may not be able to use all of the Site functionality.

If you opt-out of having your information collected through cookies and other web technologies, your existing display advertising cookie(s) will be deleted and a new cookie will attempt to be placed that instructs third party service providers not to track your future activities when that cookie is detected (a “do-not-track” cookie). If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit our opt-out page, a “do-not-track” cookie cannot be set on your computer. Also, if you subsequently erase “do-not-track” cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again. We currently do not respond to browser “do-not-track” signals.

### Third Party Relationships

Third party Links. The Site may contain links to other third party owned and/or operated websites and, where you request information from third party providers, we may transfer you directly to the websites of such third party providers. Assembly is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Assembly has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such third party website. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Assembly.

Third party Offers. Assembly may provide you with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your Personal Data that was provided during that information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their products and/or services to you so that you do not have to complete another information collection form to purchase or receive that product or service. Clicking on any third party offers may add and place cookies on your computer prior to directing you to the applicable advertiser’s site. These third-parties have separate cookie polices and Assembly has no responsibility or liability relating to them. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You are not required to accept cookies, however, if your browser rejects our cookies you may not be able to use all of the Site functionality.

Third party Technology/Software/Service/Solutions Providers. The Site may contain certain software technologies and services licensed from third party providers. Assembly may engage with certain third party services and solutions providers such as data hosting service providers, payment processing service providers, advertising service providers, and email marketing service providers. These third party providers have separate privacy and data collection practices and policies, and Assembly has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of the terms and conditions of any third party privacy policies. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Assembly.

Assembly may be using or sharing your Personal Data for Legitimate Interest purposes with third parties service providers, including without limitation:

  * New Relic (Traffic Monitoring/Optimization Services); <https://newrelic.com/privacy>
  * CloudFlare (Traffic Monitoring/Optimization Services); <https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/>
  * Pingdom (Website Performance Monitoring/Optimization Services); <https://www.solarwinds.com/legal/privacy>
  * Google Analytics (Traffic/Campaign Monitoring Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * Google Tag Manager (Traffic/Campaign Monitoring Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * Keen IO (Analytics Services); <https://keen.io/privacy-policy/>[ ](https://keen.io/privacy-policy/)
  * Keen (Traffic Monitoring/Optimization Services); <https://keen.io/privacy-policy/>
  * Google Maps (Geolocation Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * Quantcast Measure (Traffic/Campaign Monitoring Services); <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>
  * ComScore Analytics (Traffic/Campaign Monitoring Services); <https://www.comscore.com/About-comScore/Privacy-Policy>
  * Customer.io (Email/Marketing Communication Services); <https://customer.io/privacy-policy.html>
  * Sendgrid (Email/Marketing Communication Services); <https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/>
  * Google AdSense (Advertising Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * Google AdWords Remarketing (Advertising Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * DoubleClick (Advertising Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * Revcontent (Advertising Services); <https://faq.revcontent.com/customer/en/portal/articles/2703838-revcontent-s-privacy-and-cookie-policy>[ ](https://faq.revcontent.com/customer/en/portal/articles/2703838-revcontent-s-privacy-and-cookie-policy)
  * Digital Ocean (Website Hosting and Infrastructure Services); <https://www.digitalocean.com/legal/privacy/>
  * Google Website Optimizer (Traffic Monitoring/Optimization Services); <https://policies.google.com/privacy>
  * Adroll (Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting); <https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy>
  * Perfect Audience (Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting); <http://www.perfectaudience.com/privacy>
  * Facebook Remarketing (Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting); <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update>
  * Facebook Custom Audience (Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting); <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update>

### Security of Data

Assembly is committed to protecting the security of any Personal Data that is collected by Assembly. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect any Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Despite these measures, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Assembly cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with the collection and storage of any Personal Data, including without limitation, any mistakes and security breaches that may happen. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. In the unlikely event of a data breach where your Personal Data has been compromised, Assembly will promptly notify you, the applicable authorities and supervisory authorities or data protection authorities.

If you are located in the EU/EEA and Assembly is required to transfer your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we exert commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that any transfer of your Personal Data outside of the EU/EEA is protected under industry standard contractual clauses, and any subsequent data protection safeguards.

### Data Retention Period

Any Personal Data that is collected and stored by Assembly will be retained only for as long as required in order to provide certain products and/or services to you, or as required by applicable law. Any Personal Data that is no longer required by Assembly will be destroyed.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, would like to review, update or remove your Personal Data, or would like more information on our data collection, usage, and privacy practices, please contact us at:

**Assembly Technologies Inc.** #200 – 1630 Store St. Victoria, BC V8W 1V3, Canada

We reserve the right to limit or deny your request to view, update, or remove your Personal Data if you have failed to provide us with sufficient information to verify your identity. Changes to This Privacy Policy We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, update and change this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice to you. Notice regarding any Privacy Policy changes will be placed in a prominent location on the Site and will take effect immediately upon posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acknowledgement and acceptance of any and all changes.
